var MiSens = angular.module('MiSens', ['midata', 'pascalprecht.translate', 'MiSensi18n']);
// Configuration
MiSens.config(['$translateProvider', 'i18nc', function ($translateProvider, i18nc) {

	$translateProvider
		.useSanitizeValueStrategy('escape')
		.registerAvailableLanguageKeys(['en', 'de', 'it', 'fr'], {
			'en_*': 'en',
			'de_*': 'de',
			'fr_*': 'fr',
			'it_*': 'it',
		})
		.translations('en', i18nc.en)
		.translations('de', i18nc.de)
		.translations('it', i18nc.it)
		.translations('fr', i18nc.fr)
		.fallbackLanguage('de');

}]);

/**
 * Die Zahlen wurden rounded zu Integer weil ein Wert kamm mit mehr decimalen als in der Tabelle (# isovaleric-acid, Tabelle: 7742.652614 = 3, Record:7742.652614000002)
 */
MiSens.factory('information', ['$http', '$translate', 'midataServer', '$q', function ($http, $translate, midataServer, $q) {
	var result = {};

	result.datasetGroup = "scientifica";
	result.records = [];
	result.getInformationFinish = false;

	result.DownloadRecordsFromPortal = function(authToken){
		var query = { "format" : "fhir/QuestionnaireResponse" };
		return midataServer.fhirSearch(authToken, "QuestionnaireResponse", null).then(function(results){

			//results = {"data":{"resourceType":"Bundle","id":"f8ea760f-f430-462d-aa0d-584f2b91d233","meta":{"lastUpdated":"2018-03-28T16:07:58.267+02:00"},"type":"searchset","total":42,"link":[{"relation":"self","url":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse"}],"entry":[{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5a3bc885fc8d458a2d4bb3a5/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5a3bc885fc8d458a2d4bb3a5","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2017-12-21T15:43:17.000+01:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensSmellThreshold","display":"Smell concentration threshold of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2017-12-21T14:43:15.478Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"smell-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"Smell Threshold","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"isobuteryl-aldehyde"}]},{"linkId":"threshold","text":"What was the first concentration you could barely smell? (in ppb, 0 if not smelled)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":100000}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"citrus"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5a3bc8a0fc8d458a2d4bb3a9/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5a3bc8a0fc8d458a2d4bb3a9","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2017-12-21T15:43:44.000+01:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensSmellThreshold","display":"Smell concentration threshold of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2017-12-21T14:43:44.111Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"smell-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"Smell Threshold","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"heptanone"}]},{"linkId":"threshold","text":"What was the first concentration you could barely smell? (in ppb, 0 if not smelled)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":2154.441279}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"citrus"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5a3bc8aafc8d458a2d4bb3aa/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5a3bc8aafc8d458a2d4bb3aa","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2017-12-21T15:43:54.000+01:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensSmellThreshold","display":"Smell concentration threshold of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2017-12-21T14:43:54.202Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"smell-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"Smell Threshold","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"isovaleci-acid"}]},{"linkId":"threshold","text":"What was the first concentration you could barely smell? (in ppb, 0 if not smelled)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":599.486695}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"woody"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5a3bc8e6fc8d458a2d4bb3b0/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5a3bc8e6fc8d458a2d4bb3b0","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2017-12-21T15:44:54.000+01:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensSmellThreshold","display":"Smell concentration threshold of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2017-12-21T14:44:54.805Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"smell-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"Smell Threshold","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"beta-ionone"}]},{"linkId":"threshold","text":"What was the first concentration you could barely smell? (in ppb, 0 if not smelled)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":1000.380678}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"fruity"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5a3bc8f0fc8d458a2d4bb3b1/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5a3bc8f0fc8d458a2d4bb3b1","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2017-12-21T15:45:04.000+01:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensSmellThreshold","display":"Smell concentration threshold of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2017-12-21T14:45:04.723Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"smell-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"Smell Threshold","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"rotundone"}]},{"linkId":"threshold","text":"What was the first concentration you could barely smell? (in ppb, 0 if not smelled)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":0.599486695}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"decay"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5a55c8a0fc8d450baf6fbcd9/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5a55c8a0fc8d450baf6fbcd9","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-01-10T09:02:40.000+01:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensSmellThreshold","display":"Smell concentration threshold of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-01-10T08:02:33.514Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"smell-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"Smell Threshold","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"isobuteryl-aldehyde"}]},{"linkId":"threshold","text":"What was the first concentration you could barely smell? (in ppb, 0 if not smelled)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":100000}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"fruity"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5a55c959fc8d450baf6fbcdb/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5a55c959fc8d450baf6fbcdb","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-01-10T09:05:45.000+01:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensSmellThreshold","display":"Smell concentration threshold of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-01-10T08:05:45.185Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"smell-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"Smell Threshold","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"heptanone"}]},{"linkId":"threshold","text":"What was the first concentration you could barely smell? (in ppb, 0 if not smelled)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":12.91558882}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"woody"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5ab2be1dfc8d4509dc1eb95a/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5ab2be1dfc8d4509dc1eb95a","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-21T21:18:37.000+01:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensSmellThreshold","display":"Smell concentration threshold of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-21T20:18:36.578Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"smell-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"Smell Threshold","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"rotundone"}]},{"linkId":"threshold","text":"What was the first concentration you could barely smell? (in ppb, 0 if not smelled)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":0.166810904}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"decay"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5ab2be3efc8d4509dc1eb95b/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5ab2be3efc8d4509dc1eb95b","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-21T21:19:10.000+01:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensSmellThreshold","display":"Smell concentration threshold of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-21T20:19:10.011Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"smell-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"Smell Threshold","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"beta-ionone"}]},{"linkId":"threshold","text":"What was the first concentration you could barely smell? (in ppb, 0 if not smelled)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":0.464630219}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"fruity"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5abb868ffc8d4509dc1ebb42/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5abb868ffc8d4509dc1ebb42","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-28T14:11:59.000+02:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensSmellThreshold","display":"Smell concentration threshold of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-28T12:11:58.975Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"smell-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"Smell Threshold","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"heptanone"}]},{"linkId":"threshold","text":"What was the first concentration you could barely smell? (in ppb, 0 if not smelled)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":100000}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"woody"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5abb8695fc8d4509dc1ebb43/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5abb8695fc8d4509dc1ebb43","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-28T14:12:05.000+02:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensSmellThreshold","display":"Smell concentration threshold of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-28T12:12:04.454Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"smell-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"Smell Threshold","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"isovaleci-acid"}]},{"linkId":"threshold","text":"What was the first concentration you could barely smell? (in ppb, 0 if not smelled)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":100000}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"woody"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5abb869afc8d4509dc1ebb44/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5abb869afc8d4509dc1ebb44","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-28T14:12:10.000+02:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensSmellThreshold","display":"Smell concentration threshold of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-28T12:12:09.825Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"smell-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"Smell Threshold","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"beta-ionone"}]},{"linkId":"threshold","text":"What was the first concentration you could barely smell? (in ppb, 0 if not smelled)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":100000}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"fruity"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5abb86a2fc8d4509dc1ebb45/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5abb86a2fc8d4509dc1ebb45","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-28T14:12:18.000+02:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensSmellThreshold","display":"Smell concentration threshold of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-28T12:12:17.473Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"smell-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"Smell Threshold","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"rotundone"}]},{"linkId":"threshold","text":"What was the first concentration you could barely smell? (in ppb, 0 if not smelled)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":100}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"decay"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5abb9ea9fc8d4509dc1ebb49/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5abb9ea9fc8d4509dc1ebb49","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-28T15:54:49.000+02:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensSmellThreshold","display":"Smell concentration threshold of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-28T13:54:48.739Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"smell-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"Smell Threshold","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"isobuteryl-aldehyde"}]},{"linkId":"threshold","text":"What was the first concentration you could barely smell? (in ppb, 0 if not smelled)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":0}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"fruity"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5abb9f3cfc8d4509dc1ebb4a/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5abb9f3cfc8d4509dc1ebb4a","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-28T15:57:16.000+02:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensSmellThreshold","display":"Smell concentration threshold of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-28T13:57:16.090Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"smell-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"Smell Threshold","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"heptanone"}]},{"linkId":"threshold","text":"What was the first concentration you could barely smell? (in ppb, 0 if not smelled)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":0}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"woody"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5abb9f42fc8d4509dc1ebb4b/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5abb9f42fc8d4509dc1ebb4b","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-28T15:57:22.000+02:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensSmellThreshold","display":"Smell concentration threshold of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-28T13:57:22.161Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"smell-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"Smell Threshold","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"isovaleci-acid"}]},{"linkId":"threshold","text":"What was the first concentration you could barely smell? (in ppb, 0 if not smelled)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":0}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"woody"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5abb9f4afc8d4509dc1ebb4c/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5abb9f4afc8d4509dc1ebb4c","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-28T15:57:30.000+02:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensSmellThreshold","display":"Smell concentration threshold of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-28T13:57:29.334Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"smell-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"Smell Threshold","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"beta-ionone"}]},{"linkId":"threshold","text":"What was the first concentration you could barely smell? (in ppb, 0 if not smelled)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":0}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"fruity"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5abb9f4ffc8d4509dc1ebb4d/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5abb9f4ffc8d4509dc1ebb4d","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-28T15:57:35.000+02:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensSmellThreshold","display":"Smell concentration threshold of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-28T13:57:34.291Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"smell-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"Smell Threshold","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"rotundone"}]},{"linkId":"threshold","text":"What was the first concentration you could barely smell? (in ppb, 0 if not smelled)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":0}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"decay"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5abb9fd8fc8d4509dc1ebb4e/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5abb9fd8fc8d4509dc1ebb4e","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-28T15:59:52.000+02:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensSmellThreshold","display":"Smell concentration threshold of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-28T13:59:51.179Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"smell-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"Smell Threshold","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"isobuteryl-aldehyde"}]},{"linkId":"threshold","text":"What was the first concentration you could barely smell? (in ppb, 0 if not smelled)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":100000}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"fruity"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5abb9fddfc8d4509dc1ebb4f/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5abb9fddfc8d4509dc1ebb4f","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-28T15:59:57.000+02:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensSmellThreshold","display":"Smell concentration threshold of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-28T13:59:56.347Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"smell-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"Smell Threshold","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"heptanone"}]},{"linkId":"threshold","text":"What was the first concentration you could barely smell? (in ppb, 0 if not smelled)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":100000}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"woody"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5abb9fe1fc8d4509dc1ebb50/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5abb9fe1fc8d4509dc1ebb50","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-28T16:00:01.000+02:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensSmellThreshold","display":"Smell concentration threshold of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-28T14:00:00.537Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"smell-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"Smell Threshold","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"isovaleci-acid"}]},{"linkId":"threshold","text":"What was the first concentration you could barely smell? (in ppb, 0 if not smelled)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":100000}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"woody"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5abb9fe5fc8d4509dc1ebb51/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5abb9fe5fc8d4509dc1ebb51","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-28T16:00:05.000+02:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensSmellThreshold","display":"Smell concentration threshold of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-28T14:00:04.991Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"smell-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"Smell Threshold","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"beta-ionone"}]},{"linkId":"threshold","text":"What was the first concentration you could barely smell? (in ppb, 0 if not smelled)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":100000}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"fruity"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5abb9feafc8d4509dc1ebb52/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5abb9feafc8d4509dc1ebb52","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-28T16:00:10.000+02:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensSmellThreshold","display":"Smell concentration threshold of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-28T14:00:09.730Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"smell-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"Smell Threshold","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"rotundone"}]},{"linkId":"threshold","text":"What was the first concentration you could barely smell? (in ppb, 0 if not smelled)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":100}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"decay"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5abba146fc8d4509dc1ebb5a/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5abba146fc8d4509dc1ebb5a","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-28T16:05:58.000+02:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensSmellThreshold","display":"Smell concentration threshold of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-28T14:05:57.979Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"smell-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"Smell Threshold","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"isobuteryl-aldehyde"}]},{"linkId":"threshold","text":"What was the first concentration you could barely smell? (in ppb, 0 if not smelled)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":27825.62239}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"fruity"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5abba14bfc8d4509dc1ebb5b/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5abba14bfc8d4509dc1ebb5b","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-28T16:06:03.000+02:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensSmellThreshold","display":"Smell concentration threshold of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-28T14:06:02.651Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"smell-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"Smell Threshold","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"heptanone"}]},{"linkId":"threshold","text":"What was the first concentration you could barely smell? (in ppb, 0 if not smelled)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":27825.62239}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"woody"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5abba14ffc8d4509dc1ebb5c/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5abba14ffc8d4509dc1ebb5c","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-28T16:06:07.000+02:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensSmellThreshold","display":"Smell concentration threshold of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-28T14:06:07.176Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"smell-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"Smell Threshold","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"isovaleci-acid"}]},{"linkId":"threshold","text":"What was the first concentration you could barely smell? (in ppb, 0 if not smelled)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":27825.62239}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"woody"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5abba154fc8d4509dc1ebb5d/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5abba154fc8d4509dc1ebb5d","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-28T16:06:12.000+02:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensSmellThreshold","display":"Smell concentration threshold of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-28T14:06:11.741Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"smell-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"Smell Threshold","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"beta-ionone"}]},{"linkId":"threshold","text":"What was the first concentration you could barely smell? (in ppb, 0 if not smelled)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":21547.08037}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"fruity"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5abba159fc8d4509dc1ebb5e/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5abba159fc8d4509dc1ebb5e","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-28T16:06:17.000+02:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensSmellThreshold","display":"Smell concentration threshold of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-28T14:06:16.540Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"smell-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"Smell Threshold","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"rotundone"}]},{"linkId":"threshold","text":"What was the first concentration you could barely smell? (in ppb, 0 if not smelled)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":27.82562239}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"decay"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5a3bc8bdfc8d458a2d4bb3ab/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5a3bc8bdfc8d458a2d4bb3ab","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2017-12-21T15:44:13.000+01:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensTasteIntensity","display":"Taste intensity on a GLMS (General Labeled Magnitude Scale) of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2017-12-21T14:44:13.596Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"taste-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"General Information","item":[{"linkId":"scale","text":"What type of scala was used?","answer":[{"valueString":"gLMS"}]},{"linkId":"scale-size","text":"How big was your scale? (in cm)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":7.192910026854934}]},{"linkId":"scale-pixel","text":"How big was your scale? (in px)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":539}]},{"linkId":"device","text":"What device did you use?","answer":[{"valueString":"LGE: Nexus 5X (Android, 8.1.0)"}]},{"linkId":"instructions","text":"What inscructions did you follow?","answer":[{"valueString":"As part of this study you will rate the intensity of your sensory perception on a scale of all possible sensory perceptions. The scale uses everyday expressions such as “weak” and “strong”. The upper end of the scale is the most intense sensory experience of any kind that you can imagine. When you make your rating, please use the expressions in the same way you would use them in everyday life. When you set your mark, you may use the spaces between the labels to best reflect the actual intensity you perceive."}]}]},{"linkId":"2","text":"Taste Perception","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"prop"}]},{"linkId":"intensity","text":"What was your taste intensity on the scale? (in %, 0% no sensation, 100% strongest imaginable sensation)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":69.6938775510204}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"sweet"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5a3bc8c5fc8d458a2d4bb3ae/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5a3bc8c5fc8d458a2d4bb3ae","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2017-12-21T15:44:21.000+01:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensTasteIntensity","display":"Taste intensity on a GLMS (General Labeled Magnitude Scale) of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2017-12-21T14:44:21.671Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"taste-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"General Information","item":[{"linkId":"scale","text":"What type of scala was used?","answer":[{"valueString":"gLMS"}]},{"linkId":"scale-size","text":"How big was your scale? (in cm)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":7.192910026854934}]},{"linkId":"scale-pixel","text":"How big was your scale? (in px)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":539}]},{"linkId":"device","text":"What device did you use?","answer":[{"valueString":"LGE: Nexus 5X (Android, 8.1.0)"}]},{"linkId":"instructions","text":"What inscructions did you follow?","answer":[{"valueString":"As part of this study you will rate the intensity of your sensory perception on a scale of all possible sensory perceptions. The scale uses everyday expressions such as “weak” and “strong”. The upper end of the scale is the most intense sensory experience of any kind that you can imagine. When you make your rating, please use the expressions in the same way you would use them in everyday life. When you set your mark, you may use the spaces between the labels to best reflect the actual intensity you perceive."}]}]},{"linkId":"2","text":"Taste Perception","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"nacl"}]},{"linkId":"intensity","text":"What was your taste intensity on the scale? (in %, 0% no sensation, 100% strongest imaginable sensation)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":35.61224489795919}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"savory"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5a3bc8d1fc8d458a2d4bb3af/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5a3bc8d1fc8d458a2d4bb3af","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2017-12-21T15:44:33.000+01:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensTasteIntensity","display":"Taste intensity on a GLMS (General Labeled Magnitude Scale) of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2017-12-21T14:44:33.203Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"taste-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"General Information","item":[{"linkId":"scale","text":"What type of scala was used?","answer":[{"valueString":"gLMS"}]},{"linkId":"scale-size","text":"How big was your scale? (in cm)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":7.192910026854934}]},{"linkId":"scale-pixel","text":"How big was your scale? (in px)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":539}]},{"linkId":"device","text":"What device did you use?","answer":[{"valueString":"LGE: Nexus 5X (Android, 8.1.0)"}]},{"linkId":"instructions","text":"What inscructions did you follow?","answer":[{"valueString":"As part of this study you will rate the intensity of your sensory perception on a scale of all possible sensory perceptions. The scale uses everyday expressions such as “weak” and “strong”. The upper end of the scale is the most intense sensory experience of any kind that you can imagine. When you make your rating, please use the expressions in the same way you would use them in everyday life. When you set your mark, you may use the spaces between the labels to best reflect the actual intensity you perceive."}]}]},{"linkId":"2","text":"Taste Perception","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"sucrose"}]},{"linkId":"intensity","text":"What was your taste intensity on the scale? (in %, 0% no sensation, 100% strongest imaginable sensation)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":12.34693877551021}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"salty"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5a567ce1fc8d450baf6fbce0/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5a567ce1fc8d450baf6fbce0","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-01-10T21:51:45.000+01:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensTasteIntensity","display":"Taste intensity on a GLMS (General Labeled Magnitude Scale) of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-01-10T20:51:45.191Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"taste-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"General Information","item":[{"linkId":"scale","text":"What type of scala was used?","answer":[{"valueString":"gLMS"}]},{"linkId":"scale-size","text":"How big was your scale? (in cm)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":7.192910026854934}]},{"linkId":"scale-pixel","text":"How big was your scale? (in px)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":539}]},{"linkId":"device","text":"What device did you use?","answer":[{"valueString":"LGE: Nexus 5X (Android, 8.1.0)"}]},{"linkId":"instructions","text":"What inscructions did you follow?","answer":[{"valueString":"As part of this study you will rate the intensity of your sensory perception on a scale of all possible sensory perceptions. The scale uses everyday expressions such as “weak” and “strong”. The upper end of the scale is the most intense sensory experience of any kind that you can imagine. When you make your rating, please use the expressions in the same way you would use them in everyday life. When you set your mark, you may use the spaces between the labels to best reflect the actual intensity you perceive."}]}]},{"linkId":"2","text":"Taste Perception","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"prop"}]},{"linkId":"intensity","text":"What was your taste intensity on the scale? (in %, 0% no sensation, 100% strongest imaginable sensation)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":99.6938775510204}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"sweet"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5abb873dfc8d4509dc1ebb46/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5abb873dfc8d4509dc1ebb46","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-28T14:14:53.000+02:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensTasteIntensity","display":"Taste intensity on a GLMS (General Labeled Magnitude Scale) of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-28T12:14:52.743Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"taste-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"General Information","item":[{"linkId":"scale","text":"What type of scala was used?","answer":[{"valueString":"gLMS"}]},{"linkId":"scale-size","text":"How big was your scale? (in cm)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":7.192910026854934}]},{"linkId":"scale-pixel","text":"How big was your scale? (in px)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":539}]},{"linkId":"device","text":"What device did you use?","answer":[{"valueString":"LGE: Nexus 5X (Android, 8.1.0)"}]},{"linkId":"instructions","text":"What inscructions did you follow?","answer":[{"valueString":"As part of this study you will rate the intensity of your sensory perception on a scale of all possible sensory perceptions. The scale uses everyday expressions such as “weak” and “strong”. The upper end of the scale is the most intense sensory experience of any kind that you can imagine. When you make your rating, please use the expressions in the same way you would use them in everyday life. When you set your mark, you may use the spaces between the labels to best reflect the actual intensity you perceive."}]}]},{"linkId":"2","text":"Taste Perception","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"prop"}]},{"linkId":"intensity","text":"What was your taste intensity on the scale? (in %, 0% no sensation, 100% strongest imaginable sensation)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":0}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"sweet"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5abb8743fc8d4509dc1ebb47/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5abb8743fc8d4509dc1ebb47","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-28T14:14:59.000+02:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensTasteIntensity","display":"Taste intensity on a GLMS (General Labeled Magnitude Scale) of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-28T12:14:59.229Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"taste-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"General Information","item":[{"linkId":"scale","text":"What type of scala was used?","answer":[{"valueString":"gLMS"}]},{"linkId":"scale-size","text":"How big was your scale? (in cm)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":7.192910026854934}]},{"linkId":"scale-pixel","text":"How big was your scale? (in px)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":539}]},{"linkId":"device","text":"What device did you use?","answer":[{"valueString":"LGE: Nexus 5X (Android, 8.1.0)"}]},{"linkId":"instructions","text":"What inscructions did you follow?","answer":[{"valueString":"As part of this study you will rate the intensity of your sensory perception on a scale of all possible sensory perceptions. The scale uses everyday expressions such as “weak” and “strong”. The upper end of the scale is the most intense sensory experience of any kind that you can imagine. When you make your rating, please use the expressions in the same way you would use them in everyday life. When you set your mark, you may use the spaces between the labels to best reflect the actual intensity you perceive."}]}]},{"linkId":"2","text":"Taste Perception","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"nacl"}]},{"linkId":"intensity","text":"What was your taste intensity on the scale? (in %, 0% no sensation, 100% strongest imaginable sensation)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":0}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"savory"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5abb8751fc8d4509dc1ebb48/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5abb8751fc8d4509dc1ebb48","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-28T14:15:13.000+02:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensTasteIntensity","display":"Taste intensity on a GLMS (General Labeled Magnitude Scale) of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-28T12:15:12.456Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"taste-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"General Information","item":[{"linkId":"scale","text":"What type of scala was used?","answer":[{"valueString":"gLMS"}]},{"linkId":"scale-size","text":"How big was your scale? (in cm)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":7.192910026854934}]},{"linkId":"scale-pixel","text":"How big was your scale? (in px)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":539}]},{"linkId":"device","text":"What device did you use?","answer":[{"valueString":"LGE: Nexus 5X (Android, 8.1.0)"}]},{"linkId":"instructions","text":"What inscructions did you follow?","answer":[{"valueString":"As part of this study you will rate the intensity of your sensory perception on a scale of all possible sensory perceptions. The scale uses everyday expressions such as “weak” and “strong”. The upper end of the scale is the most intense sensory experience of any kind that you can imagine. When you make your rating, please use the expressions in the same way you would use them in everyday life. When you set your mark, you may use the spaces between the labels to best reflect the actual intensity you perceive."}]}]},{"linkId":"2","text":"Taste Perception","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"sucrose"}]},{"linkId":"intensity","text":"What was your taste intensity on the scale? (in %, 0% no sensation, 100% strongest imaginable sensation)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":0}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"salty"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5abb9ff5fc8d4509dc1ebb53/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5abb9ff5fc8d4509dc1ebb53","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-28T16:00:21.000+02:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensTasteIntensity","display":"Taste intensity on a GLMS (General Labeled Magnitude Scale) of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-28T14:00:20.763Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"taste-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"General Information","item":[{"linkId":"scale","text":"What type of scala was used?","answer":[{"valueString":"gLMS"}]},{"linkId":"scale-size","text":"How big was your scale? (in cm)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":7.192910026854934}]},{"linkId":"scale-pixel","text":"How big was your scale? (in px)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":539}]},{"linkId":"device","text":"What device did you use?","answer":[{"valueString":"LGE: Nexus 5X (Android, 8.1.0)"}]},{"linkId":"instructions","text":"What inscructions did you follow?","answer":[{"valueString":"As part of this study you will rate the intensity of your sensory perception on a scale of all possible sensory perceptions. The scale uses everyday expressions such as “weak” and “strong”. The upper end of the scale is the most intense sensory experience of any kind that you can imagine. When you make your rating, please use the expressions in the same way you would use them in everyday life. When you set your mark, you may use the spaces between the labels to best reflect the actual intensity you perceive."}]}]},{"linkId":"2","text":"Taste Perception","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"prop"}]},{"linkId":"intensity","text":"What was your taste intensity on the scale? (in %, 0% no sensation, 100% strongest imaginable sensation)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":3.1632653061224403}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"sweet"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5abb9ffafc8d4509dc1ebb54/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5abb9ffafc8d4509dc1ebb54","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-28T16:00:26.000+02:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensTasteIntensity","display":"Taste intensity on a GLMS (General Labeled Magnitude Scale) of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-28T14:00:25.628Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"taste-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"General Information","item":[{"linkId":"scale","text":"What type of scala was used?","answer":[{"valueString":"gLMS"}]},{"linkId":"scale-size","text":"How big was your scale? (in cm)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":7.192910026854934}]},{"linkId":"scale-pixel","text":"How big was your scale? (in px)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":539}]},{"linkId":"device","text":"What device did you use?","answer":[{"valueString":"LGE: Nexus 5X (Android, 8.1.0)"}]},{"linkId":"instructions","text":"What inscructions did you follow?","answer":[{"valueString":"As part of this study you will rate the intensity of your sensory perception on a scale of all possible sensory perceptions. The scale uses everyday expressions such as “weak” and “strong”. The upper end of the scale is the most intense sensory experience of any kind that you can imagine. When you make your rating, please use the expressions in the same way you would use them in everyday life. When you set your mark, you may use the spaces between the labels to best reflect the actual intensity you perceive."}]}]},{"linkId":"2","text":"Taste Perception","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"nacl"}]},{"linkId":"intensity","text":"What was your taste intensity on the scale? (in %, 0% no sensation, 100% strongest imaginable sensation)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":3.5714285714285694}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"savory"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5abb9ffefc8d4509dc1ebb55/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5abb9ffefc8d4509dc1ebb55","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-28T16:00:30.000+02:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensTasteIntensity","display":"Taste intensity on a GLMS (General Labeled Magnitude Scale) of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-28T14:00:30.054Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"taste-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"General Information","item":[{"linkId":"scale","text":"What type of scala was used?","answer":[{"valueString":"gLMS"}]},{"linkId":"scale-size","text":"How big was your scale? (in cm)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":7.192910026854934}]},{"linkId":"scale-pixel","text":"How big was your scale? (in px)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":539}]},{"linkId":"device","text":"What device did you use?","answer":[{"valueString":"LGE: Nexus 5X (Android, 8.1.0)"}]},{"linkId":"instructions","text":"What inscructions did you follow?","answer":[{"valueString":"As part of this study you will rate the intensity of your sensory perception on a scale of all possible sensory perceptions. The scale uses everyday expressions such as “weak” and “strong”. The upper end of the scale is the most intense sensory experience of any kind that you can imagine. When you make your rating, please use the expressions in the same way you would use them in everyday life. When you set your mark, you may use the spaces between the labels to best reflect the actual intensity you perceive."}]}]},{"linkId":"2","text":"Taste Perception","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"sucrose"}]},{"linkId":"intensity","text":"What was your taste intensity on the scale? (in %, 0% no sensation, 100% strongest imaginable sensation)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":2.7551020408163254}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"salty"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5abba0c0fc8d4509dc1ebb56/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5abba0c0fc8d4509dc1ebb56","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-28T16:03:44.000+02:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensTasteIntensity","display":"Taste intensity on a GLMS (General Labeled Magnitude Scale) of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-28T14:03:43.177Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"taste-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"General Information","item":[{"linkId":"scale","text":"What type of scala was used?","answer":[{"valueString":"gLMS"}]},{"linkId":"scale-size","text":"How big was your scale? (in cm)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":7.192910026854934}]},{"linkId":"scale-pixel","text":"How big was your scale? (in px)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":539}]},{"linkId":"device","text":"What device did you use?","answer":[{"valueString":"LGE: Nexus 5X (Android, 8.1.0)"}]},{"linkId":"instructions","text":"What inscructions did you follow?","answer":[{"valueString":"As part of this study you will rate the intensity of your sensory perception on a scale of all possible sensory perceptions. The scale uses everyday expressions such as “weak” and “strong”. The upper end of the scale is the most intense sensory experience of any kind that you can imagine. When you make your rating, please use the expressions in the same way you would use them in everyday life. When you set your mark, you may use the spaces between the labels to best reflect the actual intensity you perceive."}]}]},{"linkId":"2","text":"Taste Perception","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"prop"}]},{"linkId":"intensity","text":"What was your taste intensity on the scale? (in %, 0% no sensation, 100% strongest imaginable sensation)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":7.040816326530617}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"sweet"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5abba11bfc8d4509dc1ebb57/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5abba11bfc8d4509dc1ebb57","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-28T16:05:15.000+02:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensTasteIntensity","display":"Taste intensity on a GLMS (General Labeled Magnitude Scale) of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-28T14:05:14.221Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"taste-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"General Information","item":[{"linkId":"scale","text":"What type of scala was used?","answer":[{"valueString":"gLMS"}]},{"linkId":"scale-size","text":"How big was your scale? (in cm)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":7.192910026854934}]},{"linkId":"scale-pixel","text":"How big was your scale? (in px)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":539}]},{"linkId":"device","text":"What device did you use?","answer":[{"valueString":"LGE: Nexus 5X (Android, 8.1.0)"}]},{"linkId":"instructions","text":"What inscructions did you follow?","answer":[{"valueString":"As part of this study you will rate the intensity of your sensory perception on a scale of all possible sensory perceptions. The scale uses everyday expressions such as “weak” and “strong”. The upper end of the scale is the most intense sensory experience of any kind that you can imagine. When you make your rating, please use the expressions in the same way you would use them in everyday life. When you set your mark, you may use the spaces between the labels to best reflect the actual intensity you perceive."}]}]},{"linkId":"2","text":"Taste Perception","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"prop"}]},{"linkId":"intensity","text":"What was your taste intensity on the scale? (in %, 0% no sensation, 100% strongest imaginable sensation)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":19.48979591836735}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"sweet"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5abba137fc8d4509dc1ebb58/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5abba137fc8d4509dc1ebb58","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-28T16:05:43.000+02:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensTasteIntensity","display":"Taste intensity on a GLMS (General Labeled Magnitude Scale) of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-28T14:05:42.758Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"taste-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"General Information","item":[{"linkId":"scale","text":"What type of scala was used?","answer":[{"valueString":"gLMS"}]},{"linkId":"scale-size","text":"How big was your scale? (in cm)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":7.192910026854934}]},{"linkId":"scale-pixel","text":"How big was your scale? (in px)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":539}]},{"linkId":"device","text":"What device did you use?","answer":[{"valueString":"LGE: Nexus 5X (Android, 8.1.0)"}]},{"linkId":"instructions","text":"What inscructions did you follow?","answer":[{"valueString":"As part of this study you will rate the intensity of your sensory perception on a scale of all possible sensory perceptions. The scale uses everyday expressions such as “weak” and “strong”. The upper end of the scale is the most intense sensory experience of any kind that you can imagine. When you make your rating, please use the expressions in the same way you would use them in everyday life. When you set your mark, you may use the spaces between the labels to best reflect the actual intensity you perceive."}]}]},{"linkId":"2","text":"Taste Perception","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"nacl"}]},{"linkId":"intensity","text":"What was your taste intensity on the scale? (in %, 0% no sensation, 100% strongest imaginable sensation)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":21.530612244897952}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"savory"}]}]}]}},{"fullUrl":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse/5abba13dfc8d4509dc1ebb59/_history/0","resource":{"resourceType":"QuestionnaireResponse","id":"5abba13dfc8d4509dc1ebb59","meta":{"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/metadata","extension":[{"url":"app","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop/codesystems/app","code":"misense","display":"MiSens"}},{"url":"creator","valueReference":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"}}]}],"versionId":"0","lastUpdated":"2018-03-28T16:05:49.000+02:00"},"extension":[{"url":"http://midata.coop/extensions/response-code","valueCoding":{"system":"http://midata.coop","code":"MiSensTasteIntensity","display":"Taste intensity on a GLMS (General Labeled Magnitude Scale) of a specific substance"}}],"status":"completed","subject":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395","display":"Dick Chavez"},"authored":"2018-03-28T14:05:48.658Z","source":{"reference":"Patient/5a3bc868fc8d458a2d4bb395"},"item":[{"linkId":"type","text":"What type of questionaire is this?","answer":[{"valueString":"taste-questionaire"}]},{"linkId":"1","text":"General Information","item":[{"linkId":"scale","text":"What type of scala was used?","answer":[{"valueString":"gLMS"}]},{"linkId":"scale-size","text":"How big was your scale? (in cm)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":7.192910026854934}]},{"linkId":"scale-pixel","text":"How big was your scale? (in px)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":539}]},{"linkId":"device","text":"What device did you use?","answer":[{"valueString":"LGE: Nexus 5X (Android, 8.1.0)"}]},{"linkId":"instructions","text":"What inscructions did you follow?","answer":[{"valueString":"As part of this study you will rate the intensity of your sensory perception on a scale of all possible sensory perceptions. The scale uses everyday expressions such as “weak” and “strong”. The upper end of the scale is the most intense sensory experience of any kind that you can imagine. When you make your rating, please use the expressions in the same way you would use them in everyday life. When you set your mark, you may use the spaces between the labels to best reflect the actual intensity you perceive."}]}]},{"linkId":"2","text":"Taste Perception","item":[{"linkId":"substance","text":"What was the name of the substance?","answer":[{"valueString":"sucrose"}]},{"linkId":"intensity","text":"What was your taste intensity on the scale? (in %, 0% no sensation, 100% strongest imaginable sensation)","answer":[{"valueDecimal":21.734693877551024}]},{"linkId":"quality","text":"How would you describe the taste quality?","answer":[{"valueString":"salty"}]}]}]}}]},"status":200,"config":{"method":"GET","transformRequest":[null],"transformResponse":[null],"url":"https://ch.midata.coop/fhir/QuestionnaireResponse","headers":{"Authorization":"Bearer vZ-ZAsfgIOiw_GZ1UzRVFfqx_e98m0rj2cZrP0U-y4uroB1wQyUm_JCNEUFhBhISuhHylcFvPFhtcs4bxTpZ09xbkH9M_y1FVDKOTngZAVBHTWqhtitTeTRkaYTE00hE5If6s_NPiYBKy--U3E43CfFBbC0MoJ6_9W63x2ItwCd2rh0Z0qdqlRdqOc7WigkJ8bJHixkyIICsE3YshRfSWQWfoZkXl0ttt3BD7V7GKQb8v0tS3qCwmaU20YD9vRQoN2HcD43ZLsTi0Shv8wK_UxxpkqFZ7ApHC2HbVE_i-0c","Accept":"application/json, text/plain, */*"},"params":null},"statusText":"OK"};

			if (results.data && results.data.entry && Array.isArray(results.data.entry)) {
				results.data.entry.sort(function (a, b) {
					var _a = new Date(a.resource.meta.lastUpdated);
					var _b = new Date(b.resource.meta.lastUpdated);
					return _a.getTime() - _b.getTime();
				});
	
				//for (var index = 0; index < results.data.entry.length; index++) {
				//	var element = results.data.entry[index];
				//	console.log(index + ": " + element.resource.meta.lastUpdated);
				//}

				result.records = results.data.entry;
			}
		}, function(err){
			console.log("Failed to download records: " + err.data);
		});
	};

	result.GetInformationForVisualization = function(){
		var toReturn = {};
		for (var i = 0; result.records && i < result.records.length; i++) {
			var record = result.records[i].resource;

			if (result.datasetGroup == "scientifica" && (new Date(record.meta.lastUpdated)).getTime() >= (new Date(2017,9-1,3,18,0,0,0)) ) {
				continue;
			}

			for (var j = 0; record.item && j < record.item.length; j++) {
				var _item1 = record.item[j];
				var substanceFound = null;
				var k, _item2;
				if (_item1.item) {
					for (k = 0; k < _item1.item.length; k++) {
						_item2 = _item1.item[k];
						
						if (_item2.linkId == 'substance' && _item2.answer) {
							substanceFound = _item2.answer[0].valueString;
							break;
						}
					}
				}

				if (substanceFound) {
					for (k = 0; k < _item1.item.length; k++) {
						_item2 = _item1.item[k];

						// if information found, save it in results
						if ((_item2.linkId.toLowerCase() == 'threshold' || _item2.linkId.toLowerCase() == 'intensity')
							 ) {
								 if (_item2.answer && _item2.answer[0] && _item2.answer[0].valueDecimal != null) {
									toReturn[substanceFound] = _item2.answer[0].valueDecimal;	
									break; 
								 }
						}
					}

					break;
				}
			}
		}

		return toReturn;
	};

	return result;
}]);